Hi I'm Kim with Simply Beautiful in Austin, Texas. We're going to talk about how to get rid of dark spots on your skin.
We're going to focus on your face because this is where the areas that women are most concerned about.
Dark spots aren't really necessarily a result of age, it has to do with skin damage from the sun.
I want you to know there's lots of products out there that can work.
From very, very expensive to great drug store brands, it's just a matter of what you're budget level is and what you're comfortable with.
There's spot treatments.
There's stuff that you can put all over your whole skin.
I'm going to recommend to you that you just do a spot treatment.
I'm going to demonstrate on Megan's skin.
She doesn't have very much in the way of dark spots, but we're going to show it to you anyway.
So we're just going to take a little bit, we're going to put it on a Q-tip, you can use it on your finger easy enough.
I'll do it with my finger, or Q-tip.
And we're just going to rub it on the dark spot.
Just apply it to the dark spot.
That's all it takes.
I want you to know the more often you do this, if you do it once a day, you'll get great results.
If you do it twice a day, you'll get better results.
The most important thing I want you to know is that you must wear sunscreen.
Because if we're going to lighten the dark spots then you got to keep a sunscreen on so they don't come back.
So it's two prong, keep your skin clean, well moisturized, use a spot treatment, Clarins has a great one, Lancome has a great one, there's one called Ambi that you can get in the drug store and that comes for oily skin or dry skin, and get that sunscreen on there.
At least a 30 because it means you're prone to sun damage.